DENIS LEYZERUKOV

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Hey! My name is Denis, I have 4 years of Product Design experience making web products, apps, and design systems in eComm, SaaS, and FinTech sectors. Worked on projects from start to finish, was in charge of a small team of UI designers, planned and executed numerous user research tests, surveys, and interviews.

SKILLS

- UX Research, UX/UI Design, Audits, Design/Handoff documentation, Prototyping, Project Management, managing junior designers.
- Figma, Sketch, Adobe XD, Confluence, Zeplin, Principle, ProtoPie, InVision, Jira, Trello, Miro, Log Rocket.

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT DESIGNER

SoilFLO 2023 - ...

- Standardized and optimized design handoff process for developers, increased collaboration, and set rules for QA testing, which shortened dev sprints by 1 week (on average)
- Developed a comprehensive Design System that was absent before. Its' introduction reduced the number of identified UI mistakes and inconsistencies during QA testing by half.
- Spearheaded the introduction of Log Rocket and Mixpanel analytics suites into the Product team workflow to collect feedback, watch sessions, and study users.
- Participated in development of standardized onboarding process for new users, which resulted in 20% shorter onboarding times (on average).

SENIOR UX DESIGNER

Shopley 2021 - 2023

- Led a Product team with 2 junior designers; our team worked on 4 ongoing projects.
- Planned and completed 10 interviews, 21 usability test, and over 100 surveys and A/B tests while working on Gr8Tables app for waiters.
- Was put in charge of a project that requried development of a B2B eCommerce platform for American market of legal cannabis from start to finish.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR UX DESIGNER

Shopley 2021 - 2023

 Created a comprehensive and flexible Loyalty Program, including graphic design, marketing materials, and program mechanics. This program attracted over 10,000 new users from 11 connected businesses 1 month after launch.

UX DESIGNER

Questrade 2021

- Participated in development and launch of a new mobile trading app QuesTrade Mobile, which occupies 15th position on AppStore in Finance.
- Improved the process of opening a trading account for new clients right in the app. The process was shortened to 15 minutes from multiple hours.

UX INTERN

Twitter 2021

- 3 month internship through a University Bootcamp program.
- Participated in successful relaunch of the account verification feature.

EDUCATION

UX/UI Design & Research - Bootcamp

University of Toronto 2020 - 2021

Psychology - Bachelors with distinction

University of Toronto 2016 - 2020

CONTACTS

Dleyzerukov@gmail.com

Email

@Dleyzerukov

Telegram

+7-916-088-41-52

Mobile